<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>[Experimental]RimGoddess - Race (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.ExperimentalRimGoddessRace</packageId>
  <author>Blade of Debt</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/ExperimentalRimGoddessRace</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of Blade of Debts mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2114625254

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/ExperimentalRimGoddessRace][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/F5HDQB1.png[/img]

[b]Warning this is an experimental mod things are subject to change and not guaranteed to be stable[/b]

Adds the Goddess Race and Faction to Rimworld

[img]https://i.imgur.com/AQiiFrW.png[/img]
The Goddess has 2 forms at their disposal. The first form being their human form, this is not too different from a normal pawn apart from the need for faith. The true form gives them increased strength and durability and access to their abilities at the cost of an increased faith drain. 

[img]https://i.imgur.com/efPVNpD.gif[/img]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/UXQWY2X.png[/img]
Faith is what powers the Goddess and her abilities should the Goddess run out of faith they will go into a state of faith deprivation and eventually die. This is generated through their social connections with others and the amount they gain or lose from people is directly related to how much others like them. The Faith Pedestal acts as the primary conduit for faith and should it be destroyed the Goddess will no longer be able to gain more faith.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/Oti3gTT.png[/img]
These are the primary resource of the mod and are acquired primarily through trade. They are used to create the structure and items in the mod and can be used to give the Goddess a temporary faith boost in a pinch.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/9Py0WX1.png[/img]
[h1]RimGoddess - Equipment[/h1]
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2114625759

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]</description>
</ModMetaData>